[{"question": " okay, chandler!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " and your horoscope says, &quot;on the fifth a special someone is going to give you a gift.&quot;", "answer": "  oh, well thank you in advance.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " op, but the twelfth brings a lover&#146;s spat.", "answer": "  you are going to make a joke about my special present! why would you do that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  hey guys!", "answer": " hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s right. it&#146;s your first day! so are you psyched to fight fake crime with your robot sidekick?", "answer": " am i psyched? the lead in my own tv series? i&#146;ve dreamed about this for years! why have i not been preparing?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " no! joey, you&#146;re going to be great!", "answer": " but i got to act with a robot pheebs, and-and i don&#146;t know anything about technology! i can&#146;t even use chandler&#146;s computer except to find porn! and-and that&#146;s only &#145;cause it&#146;s right there when you turn it on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i think our lover&#146;s spat will start a little early this month.", "answer": "  i&#146;ll be waiting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " are you judging them by their covers? because you&#146;re really not supposed to do that.", "answer": " no, i&#146;m just deciding which one to use&#151;i&#146;m gonna start writing another book!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " be-because the last one was such a big seller?", "answer": " well, if you must know i have written 14 books. and as i am the only one who has read them, i can tell you that they all have been very well received.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " what are you guys doing later?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh, rachel and i have appointments to get our hair cut.", "answer": "  we do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i want to see what he wants first.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  i just found out that elizabeth&#146;s dad wants to meet me.", "answer": " wait a minute, hold the phone! you&#146;re not elizabeth&#146;s dad?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " come on guys, i-i really want this guy to like me. it-it would really help me out if you guys were here to make me look good.", "answer": " of course we&#146;ll help! yeah! we&#146;ll be here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " thanks!", "answer": " we know how tough those parent/teacher conferences can be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  so uh, here&#146;s your office set!", "answer": " wow! huh?  mac macaveli, private investigator!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  let&#146;s get you into wardrobe for a fitting.", "answer": " okay. hey uh, when do i get to meet the robot?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " joey tribbiani, this is&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh wow! he&#146;s so lifelike!  unbelievable! (he starts tugging on the guy&#146;s ears.", "answer": " this is wayne, the man who created and operates c.h.e.e.s.e.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " okay. sorry about that&#133; uh, so where&#146;s c.h.e.e.s.e.?", "answer": " c.h.e.e.s.e. is right here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  nice to meet you mac!", "answer": "  this is like the temporary robot, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " no. why?", "answer": " well, i-i just, i just it was going to be like a really cool robot, y&#146;know? like the terminator or uh, when i first saw you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i spent two years developing this machine, it&#146;s absolutely state of the art.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, it just&#151;i don&#146;t know it doesn&#146;t really look like it can do anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " this is my father, paul stevens. dad, this is ross geller.", "answer": " it-it&#146;s great to meet you paul.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i usually prefer elizabeth&#146;s boyfriends to address me as mr. stevens.", "answer": " of course, of course, mr. stevens.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " so ross, what your problem?", "answer": " eh-wh&#151;excuse me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " why can&#146;t you get a girlfriend your own age?", "answer": " that&#146;s funny. umm&#133;.  it&#146;s not funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " i don&#146;t like you going out with my daughter ross.", "answer": " okay. i can, i can see that. umm, but i think if you give me umm, one chance i can, i can change your mind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " daddy!", "answer": " fine! two minutes. go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  1 minute 50 seconds.", "answer": " okay, umm i want you to know that i have never done anything like this before. i mean, i mean i&#146;ve been in um, relationships in general, uh but i have never done it with a student&#151;i mean i not&#151;not it! i mean, i mean i don&#146;t&#151;we haven&#146;t done it. uh, i mean, i mean, we&#146;ve-we&#146;ve-we&#146;ve done stuff.  okay, okay, a joke, a joke&#151;lighten the mood. umm, two guys go into a bar. one of them is irish.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " i&#146;m irish.", "answer": " and the irish guy wins the joke!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " ross!!", "answer": " ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " how crazy that we&#146;d run into you!", "answer": " oh god, thank you!  umm, uh, mr. stevens i&#146;d like you to meet my friends uh, this is phoebe, monica, and chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " you&#146;re elizabeth&#146;s father, huh? i can see now where she gets her rugged handsomeness.", "answer": "  is-is-is there a-a mrs. stevens?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " there&#146;s a mr. bing!", "answer": " no, unfortunately lizzie&#146;s mom passed away shortly after she was born. i raised her by myself. phoebe and monica:  ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " i get that a lot.", "answer": " okay umm, why don&#146;t we all take a seat, y&#146;know? and uh, and i&#146;ll get us all some uh some coffees&#151;&#151;yeah, why don&#146;t you.  uh and you guys can talk about whatever, whatever you want. y&#146;know? whatever pops into your head.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " y&#146;know, it is so strange seeing ross here this time of day, &#145;cause usually he&#146;s got the children&#146;s hospital.", "answer": " yeah. not looking for dates.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " so uh, monica is ross&#146;s sister.", "answer": " and he&#146;s a great brother!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i had a sister.", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " she passed away. monica and phoebe:  ohh!", "answer": " oh, you don&#146;t have to do that every time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " but uh ross, ross is a great guy! i was roommates with him in college. uh, funny story&#133;  you&#146;re roommate in college died didn&#146;t he?", "answer": " a part of him did yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  okay here we are paul, elizabeth.  so i hope you guys were finding something to talk about.", "answer": " yes, we were just&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hi, i&#146;m sorry i&#146;m late but i am ready, ready to talk you up! when does liz&#146;s father get here?", "answer": " i&#146;m already here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey honey, you got the kind with the little girl, you said we were gonna to get the kind with the baby.", "answer": " no, you said the baby creeps you out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " no, the little girl creeps me out.", "answer": " you said the baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " why would the baby creep me out?", "answer": " why would the little girl creep you out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  you guys, i&#146;m sorry, could you please talk a little slower?", "answer": " this is going in your book?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " yeah, it&#146;s about relationships. y&#146;know? the traps, the pitfalls, what not to do, keep going. this stuff is great!", "answer": " what?! excuse me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  oh hi!", "answer": " hi! hi.  i think i left my keys here somewhere.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh! well let&#146;s look for them.  oh-oh-hey! are these them?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh good.", "answer": " thanks for your help.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  oh, wait! sorry, mr. paul? mr. paul?", "answer": " just call me paul.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " paul. umm, i just wanted you to know that ross really is a great guy.", "answer": " well maybe you can date him then that would save me the trouble of killing him.  are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you just don&#146;t look old enough to have a twenty-year-old daughter.", "answer": " well, we were very young when we had her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " oh. we?", "answer": " well yeah, it usually, it takes two people to&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh no! yes! of course, i know that! i just&#151;i meant y&#146;know are you still a &#145;we&#146; or are you just &#145;you?&#146;", "answer": " i&#146;m just me, my wife died shortly after lizzie was born.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  ohh. so you raised her all on your own?", "answer": " yes i did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " how was your first day?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " pretty great! except i did get a little attitude from the robot.", "answer": " damn those robots, they&#146;re supposed to be our faithful servants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " anyway, it wasn&#146;t the robot, it was the guy who controls him. yeah, he doesn&#146;t like me. he had c.h.e.e.s.e. knock over the sandwich right when i was reaching for one! ohh!", "answer": " well, why don&#146;t you just get him fired?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i may have to, i hate to do it, but i&#146;m the star! y&#146;know? there&#146;s a limit to how many sandwiches i can eat off the floor.  excuse me.  joey tribbiani.", "answer": "  joe! i&#146;m glad i found ya, i got an audition for", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": " the thing is it&#146;s kinda on the q.t. the actor who has the part doesn&#146;t know he might be fired. it&#146;s the lead in a series, mac and c.h.e.e.s.e.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " i&#146;m the lead in mac and c.h.e.e.s.e.!!", "answer": " uh-oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " joey?!", "answer": " hi ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " ross, joey is not here.", "answer": " okay, i&#146;ll just wait for him in here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " ross, it&#146;s okay. you can come out.", "answer": " yeah ross it&#146;s okay, it&#146;s me, mr. stevens.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  oh! oh my god! i didn&#146;t even see you!", "answer": " sure you did! you came in, you got all awkward, and you ran into the bedroom. you were shouting, &quot;joey! joey!&quot; bye rach.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " bye!", "answer": " i&#146;ll call you later. bye ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " what-what-what the&#151;how da-how did-what the-how did-what?!", "answer": " well, y&#146;know he lost his keys so he was looking for them&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  in your mouth?!", "answer": " no! downstairs! and we got to talking y&#146;know, for like two hours, and i really liked him so i invited him up here for a cup of coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " you were at the coffeehouse!", "answer": " ross, what&#146;s the big deal? so i kissed the guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " he is my girlfriend&#146;s father, okay? it&#146;s-it&#146;s, it&#146;s weird!", "answer": " wh&#151;you dated my sister!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " that was different!", "answer": " what? why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " this is weird for me!", "answer": " ross look, look this is good for you. okay? let&#146;s face it, so far the guy&#146;s not lovin&#146; ya! but i can turn that around! i got the inside track! we can all go out to dinner, y&#146;know? and i can talk you up! ross, the guy is a very, very successful lawyer!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " how is that important?", "answer": " oh it&#146;s important!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " apparently, there&#146;s like a million guys out there that can play mac, and there&#146;s only this one robot and this one guy who controls it! i didn&#146;t know he could get me fired! what am i going to do?", "answer": " well y&#146;know joey, you&#146;re a pretty charming guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " thanks, but i kinda have a problem to deal with here.", "answer": " no sweetie, you&#146;ve got to win over the guy that controls c.h.e.e.s.e.! you&#146;ve got to kiss some serious robot ass!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " so do you think uh, joey&#146;s more charming than me?", "answer": " yeah! that&#146;s why i&#146;m sleeping with him on the side.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  &quot;you wish.&quot;", "answer": " phoebe, stop writing about us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i&#146;m not writing about you! i&#146;m writing about other people.", "answer": " who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " marcia and chester.", "answer": " okay fine! fine! then you know what, i&#146;ll just write about phyllis! hmm!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hmm.", "answer": "  phyllis is sitting in a chair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " i see what you&#146;re doing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  phyllis sees what i&#146;m doing.", "answer": " oh-oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " don&#146;t touch him!", "answer": " okay!  all right. umm, all right wayne, level with me. okay? i-i keep hearing all these rumors that i might get fired. okay, they even have actors coming in to read for my part! come on man, you-you got to give me a second chance! i mean, i love-i love this little guy!  ah-ah!!  okay, that&#146;s why you didn&#146;t want me to touch him right? here you go! okay?  stupid! i can&#146;t believe it! god!   hey, how you doin&#146;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " so it seemed that my prom date had stood me up, so ross selflessly, offered to take me.", "answer": " what a nice story!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " so ross was in college and decided to jump at the chance to take a young girl to her high school prom.", "answer": " wow! i definitely did not see that one backfiring! i&#146;m gonna go to the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  just-just so you know i was a freshman and she was a senior. so it wasn&#146;t as bad as-as&#133;", "answer": " ross, look, i know i&#146;ve been giving you a lot of jabs and it&#146;s partly because i&#146;m very protective of lizzie, and partly because well, they just keep coming to me. but i have to admit that after all the wonderful things that lizzie has told me and the many, many,  many stories that rachel has told me that, well  you&#146;re not  all bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " not all bad.", "answer": " and anyhow, i&#146;m sorry i was so harsh before, but you have to understand that i  still look at lizzie like she&#146;s a twelve-year-old girl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " yeah. you know what? i know what you mean; i do that too.", "answer": " i beg your pardon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " no! no! not&#151;i don&#146;t mean i-i see her as a twelve-year-old girl! i mean i-i have a son, who&#146;s umm six and i still think of him as a baby.", "answer": " you have a son?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " yeah, well my-my ex-wife and i share custody of ben and umm, uh, and just so you know, carol and i are on excellent terms as i&#146;m sure you are with your wife!  oh, i&#146;m sorry!  it&#146;s unbelievable!", "answer": " don&#146;t worry about it, i just didn&#146;t realize you were married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " oh we were, but that was just a , i mean that was just a big drunken mistake.", "answer": " you&#146;re back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " you two were married?!", "answer": " oh! whoops! i&#146;m sorry, you were talking about emily!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " chandler, we said we would meet at the coffeehouse at six.", "answer": " we said seven!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " we said six!", "answer": " the only way that i said six would be if the seven&#146;s, let meet at seven, not at six.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah and if i had seven, maybe i would&#146;ve said something like this, &quot;wow! my boyfriend&#146;s such a wise ass&#151;seven!&quot;", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh my good god.", "answer": " ugh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i know what time you said.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " well actually, i know what time chester and marcia said.", "answer": " what time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " quite an interesting turn of events, suddenly it&#146;s my book to the rescue, huh?  ooh, very interesting. yeah, well this certainly clears things up.", "answer": "  what does it say?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " i will tell you as soon as you thank me for writing my book.", "answer": " thank you for writing your book. its-its uh, great book and you are the queen of everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " thanks! so are you.", "answer": "  i told you i should not wear this color.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  mon&#133;  marcia and chester are planning on seeing a movie on sunday night. marcia thinks they&#146;re supposed to meet at six, chester thinks it&#146;s at seven.", "answer": " so you knew we were gonna miss the movie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " that&#146;s right.", "answer": " inside of telling us you decided to write in your stupid book!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe i&#146;m going to lose this job!", "answer": " oh i&#146;m so sorry man! is there anything i can do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " hey joey, i want to talk to you.", "answer": " yeah? well, i don&#146;t want to talk to you wayne! i hate you! you ruined my life! oh, chandler, wayne. wayne, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " hi, how are ya?", "answer": " joey, joey, i-i-i&#146;ll g-get you your job back if you help me out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  why should i help you?!", "answer": "  the reason he just said.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  what do you need?", "answer": " i-i-i saw you on stage talking to that beautiful woman, y&#146;know sarah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " i wish i could talk to her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " what are you in love with her or something?", "answer": " yeah. her. all of them. anyone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;ve been there my friend.", "answer": " listen, i-i guarantee you keep your job if you can teach me how to talk to women like you do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i mean if you think about it, i mean ross did learn something from each marriage.", "answer": " how to make the next one even shorter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " well, this is fun. so ross, did you kill any of these wives?", "answer": " y&#146;know what? i-i-i&#133; i-i have had enough of this! y&#146;know, i-i-i care a great deal about your daughter and i have treated her with nothing but respect! so if-if you&#146;ve got a problem with me, frankly&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " are you yelling at me?!", "answer": " god no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " y&#146;know what daddy? if you don&#146;t like ross, that&#146;s fine. it doesn&#146;t matter to me, i&#146;m gonna go out with him anyway.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " well if it doesn&#146;t matter to her, it doesn&#146;t matter to me!  still not yelling!", "answer": " wow. what can i say?  this doesn&#146;t make me like you any better!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " that&#146;s okay, i&#146;m not so crazy about myself right now either.", "answer": " then we agree?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " uh yeah, i guess&#151;yeah! i guess so.", "answer": " neither of us like ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " i like ross.", "answer": " ohhh! kids!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": "  wait-wait-wait, i just thought of another story about how nice ross is!", "answer": " that&#146;s okay rach, we&#146;re not liking ross right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " well, it turns out you were right c.h.e.e.s.e.", "answer": " the shipment never made it through omaha?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}]